Hello friends, the ICC Lombard
quarter four numbers have come out. To
see how the numbers were, I'm going straight to the results.
First, the numbers are in black, so you'll have to
look at them very carefully.
[Music]
And you're seeing 538 crores from a year ago, in
fact, there's a
pretty good increase on air. If you
talk a little about other income, you can make a profit of 3 crores in foreign exchange
and loss,
which was a loss of 22 crores last time. One thing that's
quite good here is
investment income from Tal, that is, you
can make a profit from other things. This time it's in the
range of 18 crores, which was 11 crores in the last quarter. If
you look at miscellaneous income, if you
look at contribution share holders, it's 890
crores. So there's a pretty good jump here. If you
look at miscellaneous income, it's 56 lakhs,
which was 91 lakhs last time. And now let's talk about
total income, friends. So, this time
how much is the total income? 5000 to 55 crores, which was
4362 crores in the last quarter, these are the numbers, friends.
Contribution share holder front towards
access in them is quite good, due to this
you are seeing a great increase in cotton and air on air.
Now let's talk about
commission broken, it is 91 crores,
which was 174 crores in the last quarter. If we
look at the net commission, it is 91 crores, which was
around 175 crores in the last quarter
and a year ago it was ₹160 crores. Here you
can see that expenses are reducing to a great extent and going down.
Okay,
now let's go a little down and we see
that brother, it is like operating expenses,
so look at the employee remuneration
welfare expense, ₹257 crores, which was ₹273 crores last time
and ₹210 crores a year ago,
that is, the increase around quarter to
quarter was quite good, there is a jump. Now let's talk about
other expenses, on this, ₹
139 crores has been spent on advertisement publicity,
which was ₹146 crores in the record. If you
look at sales promotion, ₹513 crores,
which was ₹577 crores in the last quarter.
In other expenses, you will see 218 crores which was
247 crores last time. Now let's talk about the premium
deficiency. There is nothing here. If you
look at the claims of added expenses, then you will add all these,
friends. So the total expenditure
you will find is
3976 crores which is 4000 crores. 85 crores and a year
ago,
360600 crores was given. That means there is a decrease in expenses as well.
And see, despite all this,
in the returns under profit loss, the
company has still suffered a loss of 2500 crores,
which was 293 crores in the last quarter and
38 crores a year ago. There are
continuous losses, this is very good news
friends. Okay,
you go to the furniture and see,
brother, in the end, what you will find is the
total comprehensive income. So,
see, the
profit and loss after tax is 436
crores which was 342 crores in the last quarter
and 312 crores a year ago.
Okay, friends, so you can see the profit
after tax. If you look at it here.  Air
on your cotton water, we are seeing a great increase,
okay, so see, these results
are quite good, after that you have to see some more data,
like if you
look in the analytical ratios, you will find here that the
apps are there, friends, you can see them here, it has
increased from 7.17 to 8.89,
so you can say that this is a good result, a
great result, our expenses have reduced, there is
no increase in business, only a decline has been recorded,
but you are seeing an increase in net profit loss, so
if you
liked the video, like the video and
subscribe to the channel, this is the end of this video,
Jai Hind friends